Hi, Santosh, welcome back for your report on your blood pressure hypertension.
So I can see that your blood pressure has increased from my past visit and it's concerning.
I would say you check your BP at least three times a day, measure it and keep a track of
it.
Apart from that, you have to meet me at least every two weeks, once in every two weeks.
Apart from that, you have a serious health issue and I don't think you're gonna last
for more than an year.
So take care of yourself and just do do come back to me, let me know if you have any issues
and also be sure to do a checkup of your size, penis size so that you can be aware of the
BP issues.